<resources>
    <string name="app_name">zadaca1_SDragas</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sid__meier">sid_Meier</string>
    <string name="title_activity_todd__howard">todd_Howard</string>
    <string name="sid_meier">Sid Meier</string>
    <string name="todd_howard">Todd Howard</string>
    <string name="john_romero">John Romero</string>
    <string name="sid_Meier_Quote">Canadian-American programmer, designer, and producer of several strategy video games
        and simulation video games, including the Civilization series. Meier co-founded MicroProse in 1982 with Bill
        Stealey and is the Director of Creative Development of Firaxis Games, which he co-founded with Jeff Briggs and
        Brian Reynolds in 1996. For his contributions to the video game industry, Meier was inducted into the Academy of
        Interactive Arts and Sciences Hall of Fame.
    </string>
    <string name="todd_Howard_Quote">American video game designer, director, and producer. He currently serves as
        director and executive producer at Bethesda Game Studios, where he has led the development of the Fallout and
        The Elder Scrolls series. In 2009, GamePro magazine named Howard one of the Top 20 Most Influential People in
        Gaming over the last 20 years. He was also named one of IGN\'s Top 100 Game Creators of All Time
    </string>
    <string name="john_Romero_Quote">American director, designer, programmer, and developer in the video game industry.
        He is best known as a co-founder of id Software and designer for many of their games, including Wolfenstein 3D,
        Dangerous Dave, Hexen, Doom, Doom II and Quake. His game designs and development tools, along with new
        programming techniques created and implemented by id Software\'s lead programmer John D. Carmack, led to a mass
        popularization of the first-person shooter, or FPS, in the 1990s. He is credited with coining the FPS
        multiplayer term deathmatch.
    </string>
</resources>
